{
  
  "results": [
    {
     
      "question": " Why is AWS more economical than traditional data centers for applications with varying compute workloads?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on demand when needed.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Amazon EC2 costs are billed on a monthly basis.", "Users retain full administrative access to their Amazon EC2 instances.", " Users can permanently run enough instances to handle peak workloads."]
    },
    {
     
      "question": "Which AWS service would simplify the migration of a database to AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS) ",
      "incorrect_answers": ["2", "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)", "Amazon AppStream 2.0 "]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which AWS offering enables users to find, buy, and immediately start using software solutions in their AWS environment?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Marketplace",
      "incorrect_answers": ["3", "AWS OpsWorks", "AWS SDK"]
    },
    {
     
      "question": "Which AWS networking service enables a company to create a virtual network within AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) ",
      "incorrect_answers": ["4", "Amazon Route 53", "AWS Config"]
    },
    {
     
      "question": "Which of the following is an AWS responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Maintaining physical hardware",
      "incorrect_answers": ["5", "Securing application access and data", "Managing guest operating systems "]
    },
    {
     
      "question": " Which component of the AWS global infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront use to ensure low-latency delivery?",
      "correct_answer": "Edge locations ",
      "incorrect_answers": ["6", "Availability Zones ", "Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)"]
    },
    {
     
      "question": " How would a system administrator add an additional layer of login security to a user's AWS Management Console?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable multi-factor authentication ",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "7",
        "Audit AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles",
        "Use Amazon Cloud Directory"
      ]
    },
    {
      
      "question": "Which service can identify the user that made the API call when an Amazon EC2 instance is terminated?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail      ",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS X-Ray",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (AWS IAM)"
      ]
    },
    {
     
      "question": "Which service would be used to send alerts based on Amazon CloudWatch alarms?.",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
      "incorrect_answers": ["KDFKJ","AWS Trusted Advisor"," Amazon Route 53 "]
    },
    {
     
      "question": "Where can a user find information about prohibited actions on the AWS infrastructure?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Acceptable Use Policy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "MDLLDMMFL",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) ",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ]
    }
   
  ]
}
